Finding Aid for the North American New Music Festival Sound Recordings, 1983-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Cassettes, 1983-1993, I.; Cassette 1-390
  - Davis, Anthony, 1951- Wayang VI, 1986-04-17, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 231 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 135 Side b)
    Duration: 26:31
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_135bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_135bsc.mp3
  - Scherchen-Hsiao, Tona, 1938- Radar (1980), 1986-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 232 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 136 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 064, April 19, 1986, 2:00 p.m.
    Duration: 14:05
    Burchfield Art Center
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_136aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_136asc.mp3
  - De Mare, Anthony New work ("Spoken in silence") (1986), 1986-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 233 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 136 Side b)
    Duration: 04:27
    World premiere; Changed order from program
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_136bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_136bsc.mp3
  - Sowash, Bradley White water (1984), 1986-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 234 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 137 Side a)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_137aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_137asc.mp3
  - Ashley, Robert, 1930-2014 Maneuvers (revised, 1985), 1986-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 235 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 137 Side b)
    Duration: 05:39
    Changed from program order
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_137bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_137bsc.mp3
  - Paquette, Wayne Nightstruck III: A Blackfoot's dream (1985), 1986-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 236 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 138 Side a)
    Duration: 16:06
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_138aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_138asc.mp3
  - Moravec, Paul, 1957- Music remembers (1985), 1986-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 237 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 138 Side b)
    Duration: 09:03
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_138bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_138bsc.mp3
  - Monk, Meredith One-man-cha-cha (1984-1985), 1986-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 238 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 139 Side a)
    Duration: 18:03
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_139aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_139asc.mp3
  - Cage, John ASLSP (1985), 1986-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 239 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 139 Side b)
    Duration: 06:07
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_139bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_139bsc.mp3
  - Gena, Peter John Henry (1985), 1986-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 240 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 140 Side a)
    Duration: 09:31
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_140aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_140asc.mp3
  - McNabb, Michael, 1952- Love in the asylum, 1986-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 241 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 141 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 065, April 19, 1986, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 14:25
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_141aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_141asc.mp3
  - Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Algorhythms cycle (Version 1, complete), 1986-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 242 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 141 Side b)
    Duration: 29:04
    Performers: Tape and instruments; Jan Williams, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_141bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_141bsc.mp3
  - Carl, Robert, 1954- Roundabout (1985), 1986-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 243 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 142 Side a)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_142aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_142asc.mp3
  - Dashow, James, 1944- Mnemonics (1984), 1986-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 244 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 142 Side b)
    Duration: 19:02
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_142bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_142bsc.mp3
  - Daugherty, Michael, 1954- Walking before midnight (1985), 1986-04-19, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 245 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 143 Side a)
    Duration: 21:26
    Performers: Robert Black, contrabass; Michael Daugherty, computer electronicist
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_143aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_143asc.mp3
  - Rhys, John Marlow, 1935- Two portraits, 1986-04-20, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 246 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 144 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 067, April 20, 1986, 2:00 p.m.
    Duration: 22:00
    Performers: Spectrum
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_144aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_144asc.mp3
  - Payne, Anthony Song streams in the firmament (1986), 1986-04-20, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 247 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 144 Side b)
    Duration: 16:20
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_144bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_144bsc.mp3
  - Rea, John, 1944- Les raisons des forces mouvantes (1984), 1986-04-20, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 248 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 145 Side a)
    Duration: 15:52
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_145aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_145asc.mp3
  - Genge, Anthony, 1952- Time shadows (1981), 1986-04-20, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 249 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 145 Side b)
    Duration: 12:40
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_145bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_145bsc.mp3
  - Xenakis, Iannis, 1922-2001 Ikhoor, 1986-04-20, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 250 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 146 Side a)
    Duration: 10:14
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_146aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_146asc.mp3
  - Sellars, James, 1940-2017 Return of the comet (1986), 1986-04-20, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 251 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 146 Side b)
    Duration: 28:01
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_146bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_146bsc.mp3
  - Glass, Philip Making of an opera: Satyagraha (lecture). Part 1, 1987-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 252 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 147 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 069a, April 21, 1987, 4:00 p.m.
    Duration: 44:29
    Performers: Philip Glass, lecturer
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_147aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_147asc.mp3
  - Glass, Philip Making of an opera: Satyagraha (lecture). Part 2, 1987-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 252 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 147 Side b)
    Duration: 37:43
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_147bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_147bsc.mp3
  - Glass, Philip Glassworks. Opening (1981), 1987-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 253 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 148 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 070, April 21, 1987, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 05:18
    Performers: Philip Glass, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_148aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_148asc.mp3
  - Glass, Philip Strung out (1967), 1987-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 254 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 148 Side b)
    Duration: 19:15
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_148bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_148bsc.mp3
  - Glass, Philip Gradus (1968), 1987-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 255 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 149 Side a)
    Duration: 12:14
    Performers: Jon Gibson, soprano saxophone
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_149aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_149asc.mp3
  - Glass, Philip Einstein on the beach. Cadenza and aria (1976), 1987-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 256 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 149 Side b)
    Duration: 11:35
    Performers: Jon Gibson, soprano saxophone; Philip Glass, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_149bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_149bsc.mp3
  - Glass, Philip Einstein on the beach. Solo violin music (1967), 1987-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 257 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 150 Side a)
    Duration: 13:18
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_150aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_150asc.mp3
  - Glass, Philip Mad rush (1982), 1987-04-21, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 258 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 150 Side b)
    Duration: 14:20
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_150bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_150bsc.mp3
  - Crumb, George Idyll for the misbegotten (1986), 1987-04-22, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 259 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 151 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 071, April 22, 1987, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 11:26
    Performers: Robert Aitken, flute; Maelstrom Percussion Ensemble
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_151aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_151asc.mp3
  - Reynolds, Roger, 1934- Transfigured wind (1985), 1987-04-22, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 260 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 151 Side b)
    Duration: 18:40
    Performers: Robert Aitken, flute; tape
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_151bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_151bsc.mp3
  - Aitken, Robert, 1939- Plainsong (1977), 1987-04-22, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 261 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 152 Side a)
    Duration: 06:25
    Performers: Robert Aitken, flute
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_152aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_152asc.mp3
  - Tremblay, Gilles "... le sifflement des vents-porteurs de l'amour" (1970), 1987-04-22, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 262 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 152 Side b)
    Duration: 08:16
    Performers: Robert Aitken, flute; Jan Williams, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_152bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_152bsc.mp3
  - Tremblay, Gilles Envol (Alleluia) (1984), 1987-04-22, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 263 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 153 Side a)
    Duration: 15:55
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_153aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_153asc.mp3
  - Perle, George, 1915-2009 Quintet, winds, no. 4 (1985), 1987-04-23, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 264 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 154 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 072, April 23, 1987, 8:00 p.m.
    Performers: Dorian Woodwind Quintet
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_154aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_154asc.mp3
  - Adolphe, Bruce Night journey, 1987-04-23, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 265 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 154 Side b)
    Duration: 11:34
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_154bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_154bsc.mp3
  - Ligeti, György, 1923-2006 Six bagatelles (1953), 1987-04-23, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 266 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 155 Side a)
    Duration: 16:30
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_155aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_155asc.mp3
  - Bennett, Richard Rodney Sonata for wind quintet and piano (1987), 1987-04-23, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 267 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 155 Side b)
    Duration: 15:18
    Performers: Dorian Woodwind Quintet; Richard Rodney Bennett, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_155bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_155bsc.mp3
  - Luening, Otto, 1900-1996 Busoni, Joyce and Lenin: Zurich 1917-1920 (lecture). Part 1, 1987-04-24, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 268 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 156 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 074, April 24, 1987, 4:00 p.m.
    Duration: 30:21
    Performers: Otto Luening, lecturer
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_156aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_156asc.mp3
  - Luening, Otto, 1900-1996 Busoni, Joyce and Lenin: Zurich 1917-1920 (lecture). Part 2, 1987-04-24, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 268 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 156 Side b)
    Duration: 23:47
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_156bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_156bsc.mp3
  - Luening, Otto, 1900-1996 Sonata, violin, piano (1917), 1987-04-24, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 269 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 157 Side a)
    Duration: 13:40
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_157aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_157asc.mp3
  - Luening, Otto, 1900-1996 Dance sonata, piano (1928), 1987-04-24, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 270 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 157 Side b)
    Duration: 08:00
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_157bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_157bsc.mp3
  - Luening, Otto, 1900-1996 Preludes, piano, nos. 6, 8 (1936), 1987-04-24, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 271 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 158 Side a)
    Duration: 03:22
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_158aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_158asc.mp3
  - Luening, Otto, 1900-1996 Short sonata no. 1 (1940), 1987-04-24, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 272 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 158 Side b)
    Duration: 08:48
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_158bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_158bsc.mp3
  - Luening, Otto, 1900-1996 Song without words (1987), 1987-04-24, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 273 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 159 Side a)
    Duration: 04:06
    Not on printed program
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_159aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_159asc.mp3
  - Luening, Otto, 1900-1996 Tango (1985), 1987-04-24, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 274 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 159 Side b)
    Duration: 02:53
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_159bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_159bsc.mp3
  - Cage, John Freeman etudes. Part 1, 1987-04-25, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 275 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_90 (Box 3, Audiocassette 160 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 077, April 25, 1987, 2:00 p.m.
    Duration: 44:31
    Performers: Janos Negyesy, violin
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_160aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_160asc.mp3
  - Cage, John Freeman etudes. Part 2, 1987-04-25, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 275 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_90 (Box 3, Audiocassette 160 Side b)
    Duration: 36:52
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_160bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_160bsc.mp3
  - Cage, John Imaginary landscape no. 1 (1939), 1987-04-25, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 276 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 161 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 079, April 25, 1987, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 08:54
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_161aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_161asc.mp3
  - Cage, John Imaginary landscape no. 2 or, March no. 1 (1942), 1987-04-25, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 277 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 161 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_161bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_161bsc.mp3
  - Cage, John Imaginary landscape no. 3 (1942), 1987-04-25, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 278 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 162 Side a)
    Duration: 04:23
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_162aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_162asc.mp3
  - Cage, John Imaginary landscape no. 4 or, March no. 2, 1987-04-25, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 279 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 162 Side b)
    Duration: 05:49
    Performers: Ensemble; James Kasprowicz, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_162bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_162bsc.mp3
  - Cage, John Imaginary landscape no. 5 (1952), 1987-04-25, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 280 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 163 Side a)
    Duration: 04:45
    Performers: Tape, realized by Stephen Bradley and his electronic music class
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_163aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_163asc.mp3
  - Cage, John Music for seven (1984-1987), 1987-04-25, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 281 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 163 Side b)
    Duration: 31:30
    Performers: Janos Negyesy, violin; Yvar Mikhashoff, Nils Vigeland, piano; Jan Williams, Kirk Brundage, Robert Schulz, Timothy Moon, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_163bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_163bsc.mp3
  - Chávez, Carlos, 1899-1978 Sonatina, violin, piano (1926), 1987-04-27, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 282 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 164 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 084, April 27, 1987, 12:10 p.m.
    Duration: 07:42
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_164aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_164asc.mp3
  - Nancarrow, Conlon, 1912-1997 Tango? (1984), 1987-04-27, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 283 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 164 Side b)
    Duration: 04:47
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_164bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_164bsc.mp3
  - León, Tania Momentum (1984), 1987-04-27, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 284 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 165 Side a)
    Duration: 07:09
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_165aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_165asc.mp3
  - León, Tania Paisanos semos (1986), 1987-04-27, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 285 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 165 Side b)
    Duration: 06:06
    Performers: Michael Andriaccio, guitar
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_165bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_165bsc.mp3
  - Villa-Lobos, Heitor Song of the black swan (1926), 1987-04-27, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 286 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 166 Side a)
    Duration: 05:32
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_166aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_166asc.mp3
  - Mikhashoff, Yvar, 1941-1993 Evening dances (1987), 1987-04-27, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 287 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 166 Side b)
    Duration: 06:12
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_166bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_166bsc.mp3
  - Luening, Otto, 1900-1996 Tango, 1987-04-27, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 288 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 167 Side a)
    Duration: 03:02
    Not on printed program; Side b is blank
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_167aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_167asc.mp3
  - Johnson, Lyle David, 1949- Proximities (1987), 1987-04-27, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 289 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 168 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 085, April 27, 1987, 8:00 p.m.
    Performers: Kirk Brundage, percussion; Lorraine Abbott, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_168aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_168asc.mp3
  - Bove, Craig Piano music (1987), 1987-04-27, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 290 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 3, Audiocassette 168 Side b)
    Duration: 15:04
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_168bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_168bsc.mp3
  - Csapó, Gyula Yagul (1987), 1987-04-27, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 291 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 169 Side a)
    Duration: 11:53
    Performers: Gyula Csapo, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_169aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_169asc.mp3
  - Feldman, Barbara Monk, 1953- Two flutes and vibraphone (1985), 1987-04-27, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 292 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 169 Side b)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_169bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_169bsc.mp3
  - Kryszak, Alan, 1961- Guitar quartet: A town like any other; Air (1986), 1987-04-27, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 293 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 170 Side a)
    Duration: 09:50
    Performers: Joanne Castellani, Michael Andriaccio, Frederic Hellwitz, Leah Zicari, guitar
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_170aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_170asc.mp3
  - Vigeland, Nils Ives music: Largo; Romanza (1975, 1981), 1987-04-27, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 294 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 170 Side b)
    Duration: 15:26
    Performers: Baird Piano Trio
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_170bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_170bsc.mp3
  - Slettholm, Yngve, 1955- Katharsis (1987), 1987-04-27, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 295 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 171 Side a)
    Duration: 16:32
    Performers: Ensemble; David Felder, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_171aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_171asc.mp3
  - Mantel, Mark, 1961- From Paul Klee (1987), 1987-04-27, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 296 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 171 Side b)
    Duration: 09:23
    Performers: Ensemble; Mark Mantel, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_171bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_171bsc.mp3
  - Sharman, Rodney Erstarrung (1984), 1987-04-27, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 297 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 172 Side a)
    Performers: Ensemble; Rodney Sharman, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_172aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_172asc.mp3
  - Shapey, Ralph, 1921-2002 Passacaglia (1983), 1987-04-28, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 298 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 4, Audiocassette 173 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 087, April 28, 1987, 8:00 p.m.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_173aam.wav